<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ResearchProjectDefs>

	<ResearchProjectDef>
		<defName>MakeshiftExplosives</defName>
		<label>Makeshift Explosives</label>
		<description>Allows you to make simple explosives out of renewable resources.
Once researched: 
- Sparkweed can be planted.
- Charcoal can be made from wood logs at campfires and the fueled stove.
- Explosive pouch can be made at a crafting spot or tailoring bench.
- The manual detonator and detonator cord can be built to trigger the explosives.</description>
		<baseCost>1000</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Medieval</techLevel>
		<prerequisites></prerequisites>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef>
		<defName>RemoteDetonator</defName>
		<label>Remote Detonator</label>
		<description>Allows you to build a console that detonates remote explosives, as well as a workbench to manufacture them.
The explosives workshop can create mining explosives that can be deployed as Fracturing or Clearing charges.
			
Research Explosive IEDs or Incendiary IEDs to manufacture combat-grade remote explosives.</description>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
		<prerequisites></prerequisites>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef>
		<defName>RemoteExplosivesChannels</defName>
		<label>Remote Explosives Channels</label>
		<description>Unlocks the use of channel on your remote explosives and the detonator. Only explosives on the same channel as the detonator can be triggered. This allows to set up multiple lines of explosive defenses.
The detonator must be upgraded with a component for this to work.</description>
		<baseCost>750</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RemoteDetonator</li>
		</prerequisites>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef>
		<defName>RemoteEmpMine</defName>
		<label>Remote EMP Charge</label>
		<description>Allows the creation of EMP charges that can be triggered with a remote detonator.
While expensive, they can be devastating against mechanoids when properly used.</description>
		<baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RemoteDetonator</li>
		</prerequisites>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef>
		<defName>RemoteChemicals</defName>
		<label>Remote Chemical Charges</label>
		<description>Allows the creation of remotely triggered canisters for specialized chemicals.
The sealing foam can create walls and seal passages, while the sleeping gas can disable biological targets.
Use in enclosed areas for best results.</description>
		<baseCost>1800</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RemoteDetonator</li>
		</prerequisites>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
	<ResearchProjectDef>
		<defName>RemoteRoofBreaking</defName>
		<label>Mountain Roof Removal</label>
		<description>The destructive power of mining explosives can be focused using strong composite materials. When aimed upwards, this allows to break even through thick mountain roof, as long as the charge is properly positioned.
Allows the Shaped Charge to be built.</description>
		<baseCost>1000</baseCost>
		<techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>RemoteDetonator</li>
		</prerequisites>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
	
</ResearchProjectDefs>